Dhruv Mistry

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India



mistrydhruv73@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/dhruv-mistry-862589207

Summary

A hardworking, adaptive and quick leaner with essential knowledge of the digital and analytical world, Always keen and excited to learn more about the technical stuff,

Have had a physical experience in the field of marketing while working with the student council and the CSI-Committee as well as an important team member.

I have completed a decent research research in the field of web development all by my own through various sites which shows my passion for this field.

Currently working on my backened knowledge after my successful completion of REACT JS, JS, HTML, CSS.

Also have an intermediate knowledge of PYTHON PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE.

Experience

☆ Marketing Team Member

CSI - KJSIEIT Student's Chapter Aug 2021 - Present (10 months +)

student council

Students' Council KJSIEIT Jan 2021 - Oct 2021 (10 months)

Education



kj somaiya institute of engineering and information technology

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Engineering 2021 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications



Data Structures - Coursera

EP3KGARQ8Q6T





Skills

Leadership • English • Analytical Skills • Information Technology • Communication • Java • Python (Programming Language) • Web Development • Android Studio • Marketing